Hi everyone, I'm Russ Handler, travel agent, and did you know if you're taking a trip via rail from New York to Niagara Falls it's just over seven hours?
About seven hours and twenty minutes in some cases.
So, it's a great, quick, and wonderful way to see our beautiful country.
Here's how you book that travel.
Go to 1-800-USA-RAIL or do what I do.
I like to come here and go to their excellent website.
This is Amtrak's website.
It not only shows me my New York to Niagara Falls map, and where I'm going to be stopping in between, but it'll also allow me to put in my selection of date and time and all the information in my itinerary, and quickly come up with the pricing.
Now it's also showing me here in this case that there are multiple departures.
There are coach and business classes.
There is snacks on board the train, and there's a lot of other information that you could learn in regard to this seven and a half hour trip.
It's going to be a lot of fun, you get to buy your tickets online, pick them up at your departure site, and it's just that simple.
I'm Russ Handler and that's how you do it.